CURRICULUM VITAE

Patrick Beck Bali, Indonesia



t: +628113886687

□ : patcbeck2003@yahoo.com□ Skype: live:patcbeck2003

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Both a passionate hotelier and Asset Manager with extensive international executive management experience and track record within luxury Hotels and Resorts in Africa, Asia, Europe and North America. Passionate, dynamic, creative, dedicated and with an open-door policy. Experience confirmed in management and organization of: Front office and Room division, Banquets & Seminars, F&B operations, Planning, Hiring, Purchasing, Food and labour cost. I am highly oriented to customer's satisfaction and to resolve problems.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

➤06/2019– Present HOTEL CIPUTRA WORLD SURABAYA *****

General Manager

Surabaya, INDONESIA

Hotel Ciputra World Surabaya is a 5-star luxury hotel managed by Swiss-Belhotel International. Furnished with 212 elegant guest rooms & suites, the hotel itself has an Executive Lounge with a high-class modern décor, 5 ideal meeting rooms and a ballroom that can cater up to 350 people. Our tagline "Where Business and Leisure is a Lifestyle".

www.hotelciputraworld.com

>4/2017- 04/2019 QUEST PLUS HOTEL AND MIMOSA GOLF ****
General Manager

Clark, PHILIPPINES

Quest Plus Hotel and Conference Center in Clark, one of the region's premier hotel offerings, features 303-hotel rooms and 8 spacious function rooms that caters to a wide variety of clientele from all across the Philippines. Situated in a progressive megalopolis north of Manila, Clark has the reputation of being one of the best venues for hosting MICE. Also managed Mimosa Golf Course, with its two, par-72, 18-hole courses and the Hilltop Function Hall, a favored wedding venue. www.questhotelsandresorts.com/clark mimosagolf.com

>9/2013−3/2017 DISCOVERY HOTELS AND RESORTS GROUP:

INDONESIA

► ► 4/2015– 3/2017 HOTEL BOROBUDUR JAKARTA ***** General Manager

Jakarta, INDONESIA

Promoted from Bali to manage the flagship hotel of the company. 695 rooms 5 star business hotel with 85 service apartments, 10 boutiques/Independent tenants, 32 conference rooms, 5 restaurants and 3 bars located in the government district of Jakarta. The hotel is well established as premium business hotel in the city. Frequently used by Presidency and international delegations. Trip Advisor Certificate of Excellence 2016

www.hotelborobudur.com

DISCOVERY KARTIKA PLAZA HOTEL *****

General Manager

Bali, INDONESIA

320 rooms and 8 private villas 5 star beach resort, located in south Kuta Bali. This resort is very praised for its wedding business, and a favorite for Australian and Chinese tourists. The hotel caters to leisure and business travelers alike with its 7 restaurants and bars, 9 function spaces, a spa, a fitness center and tennis courts, a spacious sculptured pool, and a helipad. www.discoverykartikaplaza.com

TERELJ HOTEL *****

<u>General Manager</u>

Ulaanbaatar, MONGOLIA

"Small Luxury Hotels of the World', 52 rooms exclusive 5 star hotel located in the heart of the beautiful Terelj National Park. Luxury country retreat surrounded by forests, lakes and mountains. Heated indoor pool, Tennis court, two restaurants and a café, all within 50 kilometers of Mongolia's capital city, Ulaanbaatar.

www.tereljhotel.com

≻8/2009 – 4/2011 PYRAMISA BLUE LAGOON RESORT *****

Hurghada, EGYPT

General Manager

All inclusive concept. This 365 Rooms beachfront resort is located on the red sea in Hurghada. This hotel includes 4 Restaurants, 2 bars, 3 Swimming Pools and a private Beach. Main markets: Russian and British.

www.pyramisaegypt.com

>1/2008 − 7/2009

KATAMEYA HEIGHTS GOLF & TENNIS RESORT

Cairo, EGYPT

General Manager

Exclusive Golf and Tennis resort with one 18 and 9 holes course, 10 Tennis courts, health Club/Spa and 650 private villas to manage. 2 restaurants, 2 bars. The Resort is located in the suburb of Cairo and mostly frequented by the expat community. www.katameyaheights.com

>2/2007− 11/2008

LENOTRE Egypt
Managing Director

Cairo, EGYPT

Send to develop the franchise of Alain LENOTRE in Egypt by creating a new image and concept. Directly responsible of all operational and financial aspects of the business, including the factory and the 15 Restaurants/Boutiques in Cairo and Alexandria.

www.alainlenotre.com

>12/2001 - 9/2006

LENOTRE France (ACCOR GROUP)
Director of Operations / Production

Paris, FRANCE

Responsible for the daily foodservice operations and production of over 6000 daily meals, (Restaurants, Receptions, Boutiques, international events) • Total Staff 485 chefs and 11 MOF (Meilleur Ouvrier de France).

www.lenotre.fr

>7/1994 − 11/2001

FOUR SEASONS HOTEL*****
Hotel Manager

San-Francisco, USA

Responsible for the day-to-day operations. City hotel with an extensive MICE and wedding business. Total Rooms 277 including 46 Suites. Set on Market Street across from Yerba Buena Garden and just blocks from Union Square. www.fourseasons.com/sanfrancisco

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

- 2018 Leadership Certification by Franklin Covey (PHILIPPINES)
- 2014 Leadership Certification by Franklin Covey (INDONESIA)
- 2011 (CMHB) Crisis Management And Human Behavior
- 2007 ISO-9001: 2000 & HACCP Certification (EGYPT)
- 2003 2005 MTP (Management Training Program, LENOTRE (Accor Group FRANCE)
- 1998 Team Based Management (FOUR SEASONS USA)
- 1996 HACCP Certification (USA)
- 1988 1991 C.E.C (Certified Executive Chef, American Culinary Federation. USA)
- 1978 1981 BTS Hôtellerie / Restauration (Brevet de Technicien Supérieur école Hôtelière / Restauration Talence FRANCE)

DIVERS

➤ Marital Status: Married (No children)

➤ French Citizen

➤ Languages: English, French, and Spanish

> Technical expertise: Fidelio, Opera, Excel, Word, PowerPoint